{
  "topic_id":"101",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "The ________________ steep angle made it difficult to climb.",
      "choice": ["stairs", "stairs'", "stairs's", "stair's"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "In this sentence, the plural form of stair is intended. Since the plural form of stair is stairs, the correct possessive noun should be stairs’.",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "stairs": "ደረጃዎች"
        },
        {
          "climb": "መውጣት"
        },
        {
          "intended": "የታሰበ"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "The ________________ hands need to be washed regularly.",
      "choice": ["children’s", "children", "childrens", "childrens'"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "Children which is the plural form of child does not end in plural s, so its possessive form should be children’s.",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "children": "ልጆች"
        },
        {
          "washed": "ታጠበ"
        },
        {
          "regularly": "በየጊዜው"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Sugary drinks make your ________________ enamel more vulnerable to decay.",
      "choice": ["teeth", "teeth's", "teeths'", "tooths'"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "Teeth which is the plural form of tooth does not end in plural s, so its possessive form should be teeth’s.",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "enamel": "የጥርስ ውጨኛው አካል"
        },
        {
          "sugary": "ጣፋጭ"
        },
        {
          "drinks": "መጠጦች"
        },
        {
          "vulnerable": "ተጋላጭ"
        },
        {
          "teeth": "ጥርሶች"
        },
        {
          "decay": "መበስበስ"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Tourist buy many things at this famous market. \nMarket is an example of what?",
      "choice": [
        "Compound Noun",
        "Possessive Noun",
        "Object of a Preposition",
        "Direct Object"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "Tourist": "ቱሪስት"
        },
        {
          "buy": "ይግዙ"
        },
        {
          "famous": "ዝነኛ"
        },
        {
          "Market": "ገበያ"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "How do I get to Pismo beach? Which type of sentence is this?",
      "choice": ["question", "command", "noun", "statement"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "beach": "beach"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "A noun that refers to material things, to people, or to places. Example: PONY.",
      "choice": [
        "Proper Noun",
        "Common Noun",
        "Concrete Noun",
        "Abstract Noun"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "pony": "ፈረስ"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "In the following sentence, the word \"elephants\" is what kind of noun?\n\"The nine elephants were trained by a man named Zingarelli.\"",
      "choice": [
        "possessive Noun",
        "compound Noun",
        "plural Noun",
        "abstract Noun"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "elephants": "ዝሆኖች"
        },
        {
          "trained": "የሰለጠነ"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": " ________________ names an unspecified person, place, or thing.",
      "choice": [
        "possessive Noun",
        "proper Noun",
        "plural Noun",
        "common Noun"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "unspecified": "ያልተገለጸ"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": " ________________ names an unspecified person, place, or thing.",
      "choice": [
        "possessive Noun",
        "proper Noun",
        "plural Noun",
        "common Noun"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "unspecified": "ያልተገለጸ"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "I went to the grocery store to purchase some milk. \nThe words \"store\" and \"milk\" are what kind of nouns?",
      "choice": ["common Noun", "proper Noun", "plural Noun", "specific Noun"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "grocery": "ግሮሰሪ"
        },
        {
          "store": "መደብር"
        },
        {
          "purchase": "ግዢ"
        },
        {
          "milk": "ወተት"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
